{"data":[{"question":"This is the goose that laid the ______.","a":"golden's eggs","b":"eggs golden","c":"golden eggs","d":"golds eggs","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun \n+ Structure: Adj + Noun \n- Noun can be used to describe other noun but it's singular form- answer \"golds eggs\" is incorrect \n+ gold (n) - golden (adj)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This ______ looks very nice.","a":"woollen jacket","b":"jacket woollen","c":"wool jacket","d":"wool's jacket","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun \n+ Structure: Adj + Noun \n+ wool (n) - woollen (adj) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A horse made of wood is a ______.","a":"wood horse","b":"horse wood","c":"wood's horse","d":"wooden horse","answer":"4","explain":"\n-Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun\n+ Structure: Adj + Noun\n+ wood (n) -> wooden (adj)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"What was that? \"It was the ______\"","a":"door's bell","b":"door bell","c":"bell's door","d":"bell door","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The ______ were taken away.","a":"dead","b":"deads","c":"dead people","d":"dead's people","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+\"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Of course, ______ are famous for their wines and cooking.","a":"the French people","b":"French","c":"the French","d":"French persons","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+ The is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"This ______ is quite big.","a":"garden's table","b":"table's garden","c":"garden table","d":"table garden","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't like ______.","a":"war stories","b":"stories war","c":"war's stories","d":"stories' war","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The government should help ______.","a":"unemployed","b":"the unemployed","c":"the unemployed people","d":"the unemploy","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+\"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+ These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They are collecting money for the ______.","a":"people blind","b":"blind","c":"blinded people","d":"blind people","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden. \n+ \"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}